Tufts Criterion UP053
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Criterion
1968 -- 1993
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Alumni Relations
UP053
2.4 Linear Feet
8 Volumes
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of the alumni magazine, Criterion. The Criterion contains articles and photographs of interest to alumni as well as alumni news from individuals and classes. The Tufts Criterion replaced the Tufts Alumni Review as the official alumni magazine in 1969. For a short time in 1968, both magazines were produced. The Criterion was itself replaced in 1994 by Tuftonia.
Related Materials
UP003, Tufts Topics, DCA
UP004, Tufts Alumni Review, DCA
UP052, Tufts Magazine, DCA
UP065, Tufts Review, DCA
- Tufts Criterion, 1968 -- 1993; UP053.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 8 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Tufts Criterion, which replaced the Tufts Alumni Review as the official alumni magazine in 1969. For a short time in 1968, both magazines were produced. The Criterion was itself replaced in 1994 by Tuftonia.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Criterion, September, 1968; UP053.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Freeland K. Abbott; Named to list of distinguished Americans in "Who's who," p. 10.; Charles E. Adams [F 1962] married May 1968 to Mary C. Ward in Corning, N.Y. p. 18; [Adler, Louis K. D'57] Married July 1968 to Gail Farfel (Finch College, Columbia University) in Houston Texas. p. 18. Raymond Ackerman (E 1946). Names sales manager, food services vending equipment in the Automatic Merchandising Division of Westinghouse Electric Co. (includes photo). Ralph W. Ackley Jr. (1967). Married March 1968 to Pamela C. Hale (Boston University) in Wolfeboro, N.H. Administration 1968. New appointments bolsters top administration team (includes photo). Frank Alberti Jr. (1965) Recieved M>S> in civil engineering at Worcester Polytechnic Institute, June 1968. Menelaos Aliapoulios (A52) Promoted to faculty rank of associate in surgery at Harvard Medical School.
  - Criterion, November, 1968; UP053.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Trustee, Alumni council nominess are being sought; [Alumni council] Matthew Gromet, speaker; Marsha J. Ahie [J 1966]. Married August 1968 to William Kelly in Methuen. Ralph H. Aldrich (G1967) Married August 1968 to Nancy E. Cook (Scripps College) in Winnetka, Illinois. Robert M. Allen (1962) Married 9/68 to Frances E. Ziringer (St. Francis Hospital School of Nursing) in Pittsburgh, Pa.
  - Criterion, February, 1969; UP053.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    This item could not be found as of March 14, 2016.
    [Alumni council] Prospective students committee screened 500 candidates for admission in 1968; [Alumni council] Alumni leaders symposium; Coding alumni questionaires, p3; Death of (11/1/68) Carleton E. Allard (M1912); Donald B. Altvater [A1967] married August 1968 to Frances E. Connors [J1969] in Van Wert, Ohio.
  - Criterion, April, 1969; UP053.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    [alumni] Tufts men deliver health care to poor Peruvians; Donald G. Abbott (1944) (adm). Editor - 25th reunion. Stuart Abrams [D 1958]. Married January 1969 to Elaine E. Brown (Boston University) in Newton; [Afro-American Cultural Center] Opens Fall of 1969, p. 1, 8; [Afro-American Society] Sponsors talk by Hosea Williams, SCLC Leader, p. 12. Charles C. Aller (A'68) Married January 1969 to Kathy R. Goodman (J'69) in Milwaukee, Wisc.
  - Criterion, 1969-06-01; UP053.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    [American chemical society] Alumni chemists return for Tufts fellowship fete; Death of Barbara Olson Alving [E1954] June 30, 1969; Alumni weekend, 2,000 alumni throng hill [includes photos]; [Alumni day] Alumni confront seniors on issues [includes photo]
  - Criterion, September, 1969; UP053.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    [Alumni council] Alumni awards explained; Alumni ponder "Man, his society, conflict"; Alumni in residence program; Cynthia B. Abbott (J1969). Married July 1969 to Genoa A. Montgomery ('68) in Detroit, Michigan. (page 19). Jan Aillery(J1967). Married June 1969 to Joseph Grenn (1965, D 1970) in South Dartmouth, Mass. Frances Mendell Allen (J 1930) married June 1969 to Donald Fraser (a'29) in Marion.
  - Criterion, November, 1969; UP053.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    [Afro-American Society] Demands for equal employment opportunities on construction of Jackson dorm (incl. photos), p. 1, 7.
  - Criterion, February, 1970; UP053.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    [Alumni council] Sponsors alumni seminars [includes photo]; Judy M. Aaron G1968 married 1969 to Philip A. Szathmary in (Northeastern Univ.) Swampscott p.23. Thomas E. Abrahams (B.S. 1928, M 1932). Death of, 1969 (September 11). Leonard Adams (M 1964). Married June 1969 to Karen Green (University of Chicago) at the University of Chicago Chapel. Death of (11/4/69) Charles W. Alexander (E 1914).
  - Criterion, April, 1970; UP053.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    [Alumni council] "In loco parentis" under discussion at Alumni Seminar; [Alumni council] Letters critisizing election of Alumni Trustees, Kathy J. Aller [A1969], Douglas E. Knight[A1949], Whitney T. Perkins[A1942][F1947][F1948]; Jane L. Allen (J1968) Married June 1969 to Onofre Torres. Janice Allen (J1961) Married May 1969 to Joel Treiber. Reginald Alleyne (A54) Recieved LL.M. degree from Columbia Law School June 1969 (incl. photo).
  - Criterion, 1970-06-01; UP053.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    [alumni] summer program
  - Criterion, September, 1970; UP053.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    What troubles alumni? -Adminstrative reply; Death of Isabelle O. Fleck, (Fletcher 1966) December 5, 1968, p.22; Albert J. Abolafia (E 1970) married June 1970 to Margaret A. Seil (B.U) in Ridgefield Conn. p.17.; Administration 1970. Tri-Partite Board.; Administration 1970. Wave of Repression Near? Tufts Balks House Inquiry. Death of (1/26/70) Marie C. Alkon (D 1921).
  - Criterion, November, 1970; UP053.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    Alumni in New Role: Counsel Undergraduates [includes photo of Eugene Falco]; Mark D. Alpert [A1970] married 1970 to jane E. Roberts[Skidmore] in Brookline. Julius Abrahamson (M 1927). Death of, October 25, 1970.; Administration 1970-71. Hallowell Makes Public Minority Hiring Failure. [Alback, John] (1971) A Due Process Radical: The American Flag and Dallas (incl. photo).
  - Criterion, February, 1971; UP053.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    Freeland K. Abbott (Faculty); Death of, February 24, 1971, on board a ship en route to Pusan, Korea; p. 16. Robert Albert (Adm) Newly appointed head of Equal Oppurtunity and Inter-group Relations Office (incl. photo). Death of (11/28/70), Lloyd Aldrich (A1915).
  - Criterion, April, 1971; UP053.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    [Alumni council] Alumni awards; [Alumni association] Alumni service citations awarded; [Alumni] Field representatives; Freeland K. Abbott (Faculty); Death of, February 24, 1971, on board a ship en route to Pusan, Korea. p. 21.; [Admissions] How Wide the Door? (incl. photos). pp. 1, 8-16. Juan Manuel Alonso (faculty) Novelist Alonso: "I am not a poet of American" (incl. photos), p. 6-7.
  - Criterion, July, 1971; UP053.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    [Alumni council] Seminar; Third annual program for alumni and parents [includes photo]; Lawrence Altman [M1962] recieved $1,000 Claude Bernard science journalism award for 1970; Bella Abzug. Congresswoman, speaker at Commencement, 1971 (includes photos). John H. Adams (E1915). Death of, October 1970.
  - Criterion, October, 1971; UP053.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    Richard A. Abbott (A1967). Graduated from George Washington School of Medicine, Washington, D.C., May 1971. Jeffrey Adams (A 1970). Married 1971 to Alison Minei (J'71) in Boston. Andrew Ales (A 1965) Married May 1971 to Judith Galvin (Univ. of Mass.) in Boston.
  - Criterion, November, 1971; UP053.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    Richard A. Abbott (A1967). Married June 1971 to Cecille Brundeire (University of Maryland). Death of (5/24/71) Arnold Allen (M1913).
  - Criterion, January, 1972; UP053.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    [Alumni Council] Alumni committee to get it together; [Aguayo, Jose, A 1973] Biographical (includes photos); [alumni] aid in promoting new program "Time is Money" [Career Counseling]
  - Criterion, February, 1972; UP053.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    Menelaos Aliapoulios (A52) Named associate professor of surgery at Harvard Medical School; Anthony Amara [E1968] married October 1971 to Kathleen Guess in Lynn, MA
  - Criterion, April, 1972; UP053.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] Burning of North Hall closed an early chapter of New England Radio History (photo of 1922 broadcast team included) p.3. Harl III Aldrich (A1971) Married July '71 to Ruth Burnham (J1972) in Amesbury.
  - Criterion, May, 1972; UP053.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Criterion, June, 1972; UP053.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Criterion, July, 1972; UP053.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni day] Dedication of Leo Rich Lewis Hall; [Alumni council] Change in by-laws re: Tufts Alumni Status; Administration, 1972. Mechanical Engineering, Department of, Entry for: Urban Vehicle Design Competition, Milford, Michigan, August 1972.; Administration, 1972. Steering Committee: Preliminary soundings indicate urge to define aims and directions of today's Tufts as well as tomorrow's purpose.; Administration, 1972-73. New Computer System to be in operation in January 1973.
  - Criterion, October, 1972; UP053.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    [Alumni] Tufts degree prepares graduates for "nothing but the stigma of being over-prepared' and "over-qualified for jobs.' [includes photo]; [Alumni] Summer safari to Denmark great success, Directer Peter Cohen of regional alumni programs hopes to plan more trips; [Alumni] After graduation, dramatic changes [photo]; Dr. Lewis Abramson [M 1937]. Deceased January 9, 1972, Newport, R.I.; [Admissions] Opening of college shows no drop in enrollment. p. 3.; Administration, 1972-73. Shuttle Bus. New week-day shuttle ties New England Medical Center to campus, on trial basis.
  - Criterion, November, 1972; UP053.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    [Alumni] Interviews with three activist students of the 1960s, five years after [includes photo]; Aijala, Paula Rubenstein married to Eero Aijala. [Ajemian, Andre] (A 1951) Retired after 21 years in Naval Service. Mary Alderman recieved M.A.T. Art Education, University of Massachusetts. [Allen, Charles] At Tufts Medical School; Married to Meredith Avola (J71) in 1972. Death of (August 1972) Rocco Alobate (M1926).
  - Criterion, December, 1972; UP053.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Criterion, February, 1973; UP053.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    Hubert Adams (E1958). Promoted to Design Engineer; Southern New England Telephone Company; [Afro-American Studies Program] Approved by faculty, p. 3; Chairman of ad hoc committee (Russell E. Miller) interviewd, p. 3.
  - Criterion, March, 1973; UP053.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Criterion, May, 1973; UP053.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    [Alumni day] Personal enrichment program
  - Criterion, June, 1973; UP053.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    Robert Alukonia [A1958] Mangerial position, Heller Tool Division, Wallace Murray Corporation; Ralph Ahlberg [A1956]. Area minister, United Church of Christ Western New York Conference.
  - Criterion, July, 1973; UP053.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    [Alumni day] Awards to ten seniors; Photos of alumni and children, p14; [Alumni association] Awards to 10 seniors at alumni banquet; [Alumni] Filed representative program gains three, making total of 18 seniors; Joffre Y. Achin (A 1937). Awarded gold plaque for 27 years Community Service, Charlton, Massachusetts. Denise Allison (J1970) Married April 1972 to Thomas Lamb.
  - Criterion, September, 1973; UP053.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    [Alumni] freshmen class contains 180 "children' of Alumni; Alumni field representatives to have on-campus training, Alumni Council's prospective students' committee, sponsor
  - Criterion, November, 1973; UP053.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    Alumni group programs prove popular, says McMahon, regional director
  - Criterion, February, 1974; UP053.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Criterion, April, 1974; UP053.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    Alumni casting votes for two Trustees and eight membres of Alumni Council; [Class Notes] 1911, 1923, 1928, 1930, 1932, 1933, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1944, 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 1951, 1952, 1953, 1954-58, 1960-69, 1971-72; [Admissions] Mid-year admissions, a new departure for Freshmen. p. 12.; 12% drop in admissions to Freshman Class applications. p. 6.
  - Criterion, July, 1974; UP053.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    [Alumni council] Elected two members-at-large from undergraduate representatives; AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] Alumnus George McNary Jr. E1950 writes praising Tufts radio station.
  - Criterion, October, 1974; UP053.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    [Alumni council] Offers unique courses in continuing education program; Donald G. Abbott (A44). First faculty meeting; thoughts on; [African-American center] temporarily without director, program to be defered for a year, p. 5.
  - Criterion, November, 1974; UP053.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, December, 1974; UP053.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, February, 1975; UP053.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, March, 1975; UP053.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    [Alumni] Former graduate writes asking for riles of Eastman Kodak's contest open to all Tufts people
  - Criterion, April, 1975; UP053.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, May, 1975; UP053.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, June, 1975; UP053.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, July, 1975; UP053.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    [Alumni/ae] Tufts university alumni association of N.Y. dinner; Alumni weekend, 1975, Photoessay; Administration 1975. President Burton C. Hallowell resigns. [Albert, Karen (Malamed)] (J1971) Birth of daughter.
  - Criterion, October, 1975; UP053.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
    Ham Amer [A19736] Won national 15km championship race in Alexandria, VA; [Alumni/ae] Tufts is not the same; [Alumni council] Elections and activities planned, "Studalums" - students assigned to standing committees; Donald G. Abbott (A44). Criterion changes.; [Charles Adams] Presidential search is on. p. 3. Donald G. Abbott (A44). Criterion changes. Richards Abrams. "Studalums:" students assigned to committees.; Administration 1975-76. Presidential search is on. Orlando Albani (A1973) (G1973) Recieved USAF commendation medal for the second time. Robert Albright (G1972) Vice President for student affairs at Lincoln U. in PA. Joseph Alen (C1961) Minister honored at reception celebrating 40th anniversary of ordination. Louis Alfano (M1946) President of Mass. Medical Society. Death of (5/5/75) Regina L. Algird (J46). Reginald Alleyne (A54) Visiting professor of law at Boston University.
  - Criterion, November, 1975; UP053.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
    [Alumni/ae] Alumni survey; [Alumni council] Souffle nights, marionette days: continuing education programs; David Altschuler [D1936] died 4/20/75; Bruce P. Abbott (M75). Interning at Rhode Island Hospital, Providence. (page 13). Cindy Abbott (A69). Wage and salary analyst at NEMC [New England Medical Center], Boston. (page 12). Richard Alley (A49) Director of Health Services at William and Mary College honored. James F. Allison (A72) Secondary science instructor for schools in Manchester.
  - Criterion, December, 1975; UP053.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    Donald G. Abbott [A1944] New director of estate resources; [Alumni council] A trustee's views on search for new president
  - Criterion, February, 1976; UP053.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
    [American civil liberties union] Abortion issue will disappear; [Alumni weekend] Planning for alumni return underway; [Alumni council] Tribute to lifelong active alumnus, Nominating committee, ballots; [Sam Altreuter][E1976] sailors perfect; [Adkins, Alison (Corner)] Brief details; married Adkins, Robert H. (Harvard). p. 12.; Administration 1976. Graduate education wound up. [Ainslee Jr, Dr. William H. (9A 69)] Brief details; married Mitchell, Marilyn. Alethea Sorority gift. Dr. Menelaos A. Aliapoulios (A52) Brief Details. [Alma Mater][Alumni 1976] Pushing Alma Mater out on ice to die, p. 6. [Alumni 1976] Bicentennial celebrations, p. 7,13. [Alumni 1976] Ballot for alumni trustee, p. 14.
  - Criterion, March, 1976; UP053.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Criterion, May, 1976; UP053.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    [Alumni day] Working as an annual fund volunteer; [Alumni council] Working as an annual fund volunteer; [Alumni] The gospel according to Hairston, Jester; Tufts Medical Alumni Weekend: working as an annual fund volunteer; [Alumni] Jeffrey Robison, California dreaming; [Alumni] Rich Giachetti, of meatballs and fastbnalls; Dr Albert. A Altavesta[D1938] died 3/3/1976; Alison (Minet) Adams (J1971) announces birth of son. p. 15. Jeffrey Adams. Brief details; announces birth of son.; [Admissions] Behnke, Michael to replace Palmer, John as dean of undergraduate admissions. p. 4. Julian H. Allen (A42) Brief details. [Alumni 1976] Untypically speaking, p.2.
  - Criterion, July, 1976; UP053.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    [Alumni association] Greetings from Berberati, letter; [Alumni] Greeting for Berberati, letter; [Alumni] Alexander McFarlene [A34]pp12-13; Sam Altreuter [E1976] wins Houston award, named member of All-American sailing team; Donald G. Abbott (A44). Recipient of Distinguished Service Award (1975) Philip H. Abelson. Appalled senior; letter. Philip H. Abelson. Abelson on human uncertainty. Richards B. M. Abrams [A76]. Recipient of Senior Award. Philip H. Abelson. Recipient of honorary degree.
  - Criterion, October, 1976; UP053.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] Tufts in Sahara, 2; [Alumni] Next time use Tri-X; Alumni trustees, 8; [Aluni] Gabriella Jeppson, she runs the only all modern art show in town; Officially open for alumni business, 26; Academie des Sciences; Mayer, Jean enters Academie; P.7. David C. Albert (A76) Class notes: Married Laurie C. Gilbert (Brandeis). Death of (6/4/76) Dr. Leon T. Alley (M15). Dr. Myron Allukian (A60) Class notes.
  - Criterion, December, 1976; UP053.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    Harold E. Adams Jr. (A45). Class notes. Dr. Louis Albert (M30) Died 9/20/76; Jay Altmayer [A1972] married Marjorie Shufro[J1972]
  - Criterion, February, 1977; UP053.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
    Mitchel Abolafia (A74) mentioned in class notes. p. 12. David Abramson. Class notes; announces brth of daughter.Lynette (Davis) Abramson [Bouve67]. Class notes; announces birth of daughter.Bella Abzug. The lecture circuit.Theodore C. Achilles Jr. (F62). Class notes.Rev. Eugene Adams (A71). Class notes. Capt. Randolph K. Adams (A70). Class notes.; [Admissions] Admissions in a bear market. pp. 8, 9, 15. [Alonso, Juan M.] Author of novel "Althea, or the Divorce of Adam and Eve". [Alumni 1977] More fund people; Moynihan, Sen. Daniel Patrick; Farewell to academe, p. 4.
  - Criterion, April, 1977; UP053.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
    [Alumni association] Our goof; Henry L. Adams (A25). Died December 12, 1976.; [Admissions] Admissions in a bear market (part II). pp. 6, 7. [Akerson, Charles B.] (A45) Class notes. Edwin C. Allen (A65) Class notes. [Alumni 1977] Salute, p. 2. [Alumni 1977] Alumni trustee candidates named, p.2.
  - Criterion, June, 1977; UP053.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    [American film institute] Andre Guttfreund wins Oscar, Sharon Mann wins Better Davis award; [Alumni association] Tripping; Jean Abounder (G68). Class notes. Academy Awards; Guttfreund, Andre wins Oscar; P.17. David M. Adamson (F'73). Class notes.; [Admissions] [Alumni 1977] Admissions and the legacy. p. 2.; [Adzigian, Dr. Ned M42] Class notes. p. 13; [African-American Culture Center] Black writers, p. 4, 5; Center new foci, p. 5. capt. Orlando J. Albani Jr. (A71) Class notes. [Alumni 1977] Alumni discounts, p. 4.
  - Criterion, July, 1977; UP053.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
    [Alumni day] Photoessay, Class of 1927; [Alumni council] Election results; [Alumni association] Recipients of distinguished service awards named; Janet Adams (G77). Notre Dame de Charette; [African-American Center] [Alumni 1977] Black alumni and alumnae, p. 2. Dr. Myron Allukian (A60) Class notes. [Alumni 1977] Orientation for life, pg. 2. O'Donnell, Virginia Ramsdell; the 50s look good at last, p. 15.
  - Criterion, October, 1977; UP053.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. John R. Ambacher [F1967]class notes; "An Accident of iconography or goddess in our midst?" Article written by Gruber, Lucretia (fac.) p. 6, 7; [Admissions] How it happened (over enrollment). p. 3.; [Department of Agriculture, 1977] Department plans research center. [Dr. Louis F. Alfano] (M46) Class notes. Death of (4/2/77) George W. Allen (A41). [Alumni 1977] Tufts oldest alumnae; Dewick, Cora Polk dies, p.5.
  - Criterion, December, 1977; UP053.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. William H. Ainslee. Class notes; announces birth of son.
  - Criterion, February, 1978; UP053.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
    [Alumni council] Departmental friends, Getting it straight; Mark D. Alpert [A70] Clas notes. David Adamson (F73). Class notes. Harl "Hap" Aldrich (A71). Class notes. Death of (8/18/77) Haig S. Alemian (USN 1961). [Alessandro, Kent T.] (F74) Class notes. Neil A. Allen (F76) Class notes. [Alumni 1978] Hot phone, p. 2.
  - Criterion, April, 1978; UP053.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. John R. Ambacher [F1967] class notes; Alumni weekend; Judy A. (Uhle) Aaronson F64 Class Notes p. 18. Lawrence M. Abrams (A59). Class notes. Dr. Edmund F. Ackell (D53). Class notes.; Mohiuddin Ahmad [F55]. Class notes.; Fakhruddin Ahmed [F55]. Class notes. Charles B. Akerson [A47]. Class notes. M. Rafet akgunay [F76]. Class notes. Khaled M. Al-Fayez [F70]. Class notes. Bakhtiar Ali (F57) Class notes. Darien Alpern [A73] Class Notes. [Alumni 1978] Alumni trustee ballots due; candidates named, p. 3,4. [Alumni 1978] Forman, Dave; staving off anxiety in NH, p. 8. [Alumni 1978] Payne, Stephen; finding his style, pg. 8.
  - Criterion, June, 1978; UP053.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
    [American film institute] Tufts in Hollywood, Margaret "Peggy" King; [Alumni council] Two new trustees: Thomas O'Brien and Rosalyn Berenberg; Judith Alter brief details, p. 18; J. Byron Fleck (Fletcher 1976) Class Notes, p. 18; AIAA (American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics) Frank Ya; new members inducted, p 5; Janet I. Adams (F76). Class notes.; Anak A. G. Agung [F73]. Class notes.; Alberto Agucia [F76]. Class notes. Alam, A. W. Shamus-Ul [F86]. Class notes. [Alumni 1978] Today's grades for yesterday's students, p. 4. [Alumni 1978] Pepe, Charlie; Charlie's gangersters, no page #.
  - Criterion, July, 1978; UP053.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    Photoessay; [Alumni day] 50th reunion class on Alumni day [includes photo]; Herbert Abrams. Service citation recipient.; [Admissions] A startling increase. p. 4.; Marco A. Aguilar [F77]. Class notes. Dr. Theodore J. Albertowicz (M40) Died 2/26/78. Death of (3/27/78) Dr. Robert J. Allen (D18). [Alumni 1978] BSOT [Boston School of Occupational Therapy] second class status, p. 2. [Alumni 1978] Alumni et Alumnae Tuftensis Universitatis, p. 17.
  - Criterion, October, 1978; UP053.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
    [Ed Adamovicz] Sportshorts: new jobs. p. 7; [Ed Adamovicz] Sportshorts: new jobs. p. 7; [Alumni/ae] Office of career guidance and placement to destroy inactive files
  - Criterion, December, 1978; UP053.001.004.00008 (Box 4)